A Guide to the League of Women Voters of Virginia records, 1920-2011
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Administrative records., Extent: 21 boxes. (Box 18-38)
  - Subseries 12: Public Relations., 1 box (Box 24)
    - Papers, 1991, 1996, 2006, no date. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Tips on Reaching the Public. (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 13: Publications., 1 box (Box 24)
    - Chairman, 1957-1965. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Report, 1996. (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 14: State Observer Corps., 1 box (Box 25)
    - Papers, 1981, 1990-1994. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 15: Miscellaneous Committees., 1 box (Box 25)
    - Think Tank committee, 1970. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Committees--miscellaneous papers, 1979-1987. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 16: Education Fund., 1 box (Box 25)
    - Papers, 1980-1985. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Papers, 1986. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Papers, 1987. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Papers, 1988, 1990-1992. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 17: Rosters., 1 box (Box 25)
    - Rosters, 1960-1962. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Rosters, 1963-1964. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Rosters, 1965. (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Rosters, 1966. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Rosters, 1967. (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Rosters, 1968-1969. (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Rosters, 1970-1973, 1981. (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Rosters, 2005-2007, no date. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 18: Adminstrative handbook., 1 box (Box 26)
    - Handbooks. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Administrative handbook materials and draft. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 19: Reports., 1 box (Box 26)
    - Annual reports, state chapter, 1954-1958. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Annual reports, state chapter, 1963-1965. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Annual reports, local chapters, 1957. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Annual reports, local chapters, 1958. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - State board report, 1979. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - State and local leagues annual report, section II, 1980, 1981. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Reports, 2003-2005. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 20: Actions., 2 boxes (Box 26-27)
    - Miscellaneous actions, 1954-1962. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Action, 1973-1979. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Action, 1980-1985. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Action, 1986-1987. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Action, 1988-1989. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Action, 198[-]. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Action, 1990-1991. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Action, March-October 1992. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Action, November-December, no date, 1992. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Action, January-February 1993. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Action, March-December, no date, 1993. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Postitioned for Action, 1993. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Action, 1994-1995. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Action, 1996, 1998-1999, 199[-]. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Action, 2004, 2007. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 21: Positions., 2 boxes (Box 27-28)
    - Positions, 1969. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Positions, 1975-1977, 1980-1983. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Positions, 1984-1989, no date. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Positions, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Positioned for Action, 1993. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Positions, 1994-1999, no date. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Positions, 2005, 2007. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 22: Planning., 2 boxes (Box 28-29)
    - Program planning, 1956-1960. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Program planning, 1961-1963. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Program planning, 1964. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Program planning, 1965-1966. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Program planning, 1967. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Program planning, 1968-1969, 196[-]. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Program planning, 1970-1971, 1973. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Program planning, 1974-1979. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Program planning, 1980-1982. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Program planning, 1983-1985. (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Program planning, 1986-1987. (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Program planning, 1988-1989, 198[-]. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Program planning, 1990-1995, 199[-]. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Program planning, 2001, 2005-2006. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Strategy planning worksheets. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Long range planning, 1983-1988. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 23: Projects., 1 box (Box 29)
    - Project reports, completed, 1983-1992. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Project requests and responses, 1980-1988. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 24: Consensus and Concurrence., 1 box (Box 29)
    - Consensus, 1958-1969. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Consensus, 1973-1974, 1976. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Consensus, 1981, 1983-1986, 198[-], 1993. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Concurrence, 1973, 1980, 1985, 1988-1992, 1996, no date. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 25: Lobbying., 2 boxes (Box 29-30)
    - Lobbying, 1973-1979. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Lobbying, 1980-1982. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Lobbying, 1983-1985. (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Lobbying, 1986-1987. (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Lobbying, 1988-1989, 198[-]. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Lobbying, 1995-1996. (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Lobbyists--expenses, 1990-1993, 1996. (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Lobbying, no date. (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Lobbying workshops, 1981-1983, 1985. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Lobbying workshop, 1986. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Lobbying workshop, 1989. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Lobbying workshop, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Lobbying workshop, 1993. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 26: Conferences and Roundtables., 3 boxes (Box 30-32)
    - Progress conference, 1955. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - League program conferences, 1962-1964. (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Legislative conferences, 1963-1966. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Legislative conference workshops, 1958-1963. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Education Roundtable, 1983-1987. (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 1981, 1984-1988. (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 1989 session. (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 1990 session. (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 1991 session. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 1992 session. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 1993 session. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 1994 session. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 1995 session. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 1996 session. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 1998 session. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 1999 session. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2000 session. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2001 session. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2002 session. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2005 session. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2006 session (folder 1 of 2). (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2006 session (folder 2 of 2). (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2007 session (folder 1 of 2). (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2007 session (folder 2 of 2). (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2007 session (Olga Hernandez, LWV VA vice president). (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2007 session (Molly O'Brien, LWV VA Publications/Arrangements). (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2008 session. (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2009 session. (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, 2010 session. (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable, no date. (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable internship. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable conference, 1986. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable conference, 1987. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Women's Legislative Roundtable conference, 1988. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 27: Workshops., 2 boxes (Box 32-33)
    - Fall workshop, 1969. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Fall workshops, 1979-1983. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Fall workshops, 1985-1986. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Fall workshop, 1988. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Fall workshop, 1989. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Fall workshops, 1995-1996. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Fall workshops, 1998-1999. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Fall workshops, 2003. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Fall workshops, 2004 (sample member packet). (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Fall workshops, 2004 (Molly O'Brien, LWV VA, Board--event/publications). (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Fall workshops, 2004 (materials). (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Fall workshops, 2005. (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Fall workshops, 2005 (fundraising). (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Fall workshops, 2005 (membership). (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Fall workshops, 2005 (redistricting). (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Fall workshops, 2005 (Molly O'Brien, LWV VA, Board--events/publications. (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Fall workshops, 2006. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Fall workshops, 2006 (Olga Hernandez, LWV VA, Board--vice president). (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Fall workshops, 2006 (Molly O'Brien, LWV VA, Board--events/publications). (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Fall workshops, 2006 (office copy, pres packet, attendee packets). (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Fall workshops, 2007. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Fall workshops, 2008. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Fall workshops, 2009. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Fall workshops, 2010. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Convention workshop, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Valley regional workshop, 1982. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 28: League Day/Lobby Day., 1 box (Box 33)
    - League Day, 1980-1992. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - League Day, 1993-1994, no date. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - League Day, 2001. (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - League Day, 2003. (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Lobby Day, 2006. (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Lobby Day, 2007. (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Lobby Day, 2008. (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Lobby Day, 2009. (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Lobby Day, 2011. (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 29: Coalitions and affiliates., 2 boxes (Box 33-34)
    - Coalitions and affiliates, 1975-1978, 1981-1984. (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Coalitions and affiliates, 1985-1986. (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Coalitions and affiliates, 1987-1989, 198[-]. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Coalitions and affiliates, 1990-1991. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Coalitions and affiliates, 1992-1993. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Coalitions and affiliates, 1994-1995. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Coalitions and affiliates, 1999-2000, 2004, no date. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Coalition review committee, 1986-1992. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Coalition list, 1991-1993. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 30: History., 2 boxes (Box 34-35)
    - League of Women Voters 50th anniversary. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - League of Women Voters 60th anniversary. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - League of Women Voters 75th anniversary. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - League of Women Voters 89th anniversary. (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - League of Women Voters 90th anniversary. (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Equal Suffrage League 100th anniversary. (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Commerative coin, 1970. (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Histories and related papers. (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Histories of state positions, 1970, 1975-1980, 1996. (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Clippings, 1980-1981. (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - News releases, 1981-1986. (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Clippings, 1982-1987, 1994. (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Scrapbook, 1920-1923, clippings. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1920-1923, correspondence. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook, 1920-1923, miscellaneous materials, pamphlets, and rosters. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbooks, 1957-1961, 1974-1977 (located in collection oversize boxes 78 and 79). (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Audio recordings, 1965, no date. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Cook book. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Photograph--LWV VA president Freda Wenditz, Virginia State Senator Yvonne Miller, and Richmond league president Amy Burgett, ca. 2001-2003. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 31: Correspondence., 2 boxes (Box 35-36)
    - Correspondence, general, 1983-1988. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, general, 1989. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, general, 1990-1993, 1995, 1999. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, general, 2001-2004. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, general, July-September 2007. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, general, October-December, no date, 2007. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, general, January-August 2008. (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, general, September-December 2008. (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, general, January-July 2009. (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, general, August-October, no date, 2009. (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, general, January-April 2010. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, general, August-December, no date 2010. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, general, 2011. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Monthly contacts and correspondence, 1975. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 32: State Board Papers., 1 box (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1977-1983. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1984-1997. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 2003-2006. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous papers, no date. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 33: Jobs Analysis., 1 box (Box 36)
    - Jobs analysis, description, etc.--Secretary, 1960-1965. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Jobs analysis, description, etc., 1966-1968, 1974-1975, 1982, 1986, 1992. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 34: Leadership., 1 box (Box 36)
    - Leadership training. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Liaison leaders, 1985-1987, 1993-1995. (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Liaison leaders, 2005, 2008-2009, no date. (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Guides for discussion leaders. (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 35: Miscellaneous files., 2 boxes (Box 36-37)
    - Calendars, 1997-2010. (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Meetings, region III, 1990. (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Skills surveys. (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Tour of strip mine area, April 1977. (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Other state leagues, 1974, 1987-1988, 1991-1993. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Communications, 1993. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Non-league speaking engagements, 1978, 1982-1983. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Resource material. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Mimeo request forms and note cards (blank). (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Certificates (blank). (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Sample letters and forms. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Stationary--ordering. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Filing tips. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 36: League of Women Voters of the United States., 2 boxes (Box 37-38)
    - By-laws of the League of Women Voters of the United States. (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Convention, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Convention, 1998. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Convention, 2000. (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Convention, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - 1988 Presidential debates, 1985-1988. (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - 1988 Presidential debates clippings, 1988. (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - 1992 Presidential debates, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Long range plan, 1988. (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - National continuing responsibilities, 1960-1966. (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - National program planning, 1964, 1966, 1985, 1986, 1989, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Impact on Issues, 1976-1978: A Leader's Guide to National Program. (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Education Fund, 1965, 1987, 1991-1992. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Education Fund, 1993, 1995, no date. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Overseas Education Fund, 1964-1965, 1967, no date. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Crossroads, 1991. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Crossroads, January-February 1992. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Crossroads, March-November 1992. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Crossroads, 1993-1994. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Crossroads, no date. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Voting requirements survey--Virginia. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1959, 1963, 1965. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1978, 1980, 1985-1988, 1990. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1991. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1993, 1995, 1999. (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 2003-2005. (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Subject files., Extent: 22 boxes. (Box 39-60)
  Subject files consists of advertisements, brochures, clippings, contracts, correspondence, flyers, legislation, lists, newsletters, publications, questionnaires, reports, studies, testimonies, and other materials concerning women and women's rights, children, civil rights, education, elections and voting rights, environment, government and politics, health and mental health, international relations, justices, property rights and land use, taxation and finances, Virginia, welfare, and other topics.
  - Subseries 1: Elections., 3 boxes (Box 39-41)
    - Bond referendum, 1977. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - General, 1978. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - General, 1980. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Veto override session amendment, 1980. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - veto override session amendment clippings, 1980. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - General, 1981. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Gubernatorial debate, February-May 1981. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Gubernatorial debate, June-August 1981. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Gubernatorial debate, September 1981. (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Gubernatorial debate, October-November 1981. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Gubernatorial debate, no month 1981,. (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - General, 1982. (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Ballot question #3 limiting legislation introduced in short session, September-13 October 1982. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Ballot question #3 limiting legislation introduced in short session, 14 October-November, no month 1982 (also April 1983). (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - General, 1983. (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - General, 1984. (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - U.S. Senate debates, May-June 1984. (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Senate debates, July 1984. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - U.s. Senate debates, August 1984. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Senate debates, September 1984. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Senate debates, October-November, no date 1984 (also April 1985). (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - General, 1985. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - State Board of Elections, 1985. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - General, 1986. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - General, 1987. (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Lottery, 1987. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - General, 1988. (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Super Tuesday primary, 8 March 1988. (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Senate debate, 1988. (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - General, 1989. (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Gubernatorial debate, 1989. (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - General, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - General, 1991. (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - General, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Ballot issues, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Ross Perot and ballot access, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - General, 1993. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Gubernatorial debate, 1993. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - General, 1994. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Senate debate, 1994. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - General, 1996. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Gubernatorial debate, 1997. (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Constitutional amendments, 1998. (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - General, 2001. (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - General, 2002. (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - General, 2003. (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - General, 2004. (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - General, 2005. (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Gubernatorial debate, 2005. (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - U.S. Senate Debate, 2006. (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Marriage amendment, 2006. (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - General, 200[-]. (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - ABC precinct reporting and exit polling, 1970, 1976-1977, 1980-1984. (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - ABC precinct reporting and exit polling, 1985-1988, 1992-1993. (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 2: Election laws., 2 boxes (Box 41-42)
    - Election laws, 1961-1962. (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Election laws, January-18 October 1963. (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Election laws, 21 October-December, no month 1963. (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Election laws, 1964. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Election laws, 1965-1966. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Election laws, 1967-1969, 196[-]. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Election laws, 1970-1971, 1973. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Election laws, 1974-1976, 1979. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Election laws, 1980-1984. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Election laws, 1985-1987. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Election laws, 1990-1992. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Election laws, 1993, 199[-]. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Election laws, 2005, no date. (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 3: Voters and Voting Rights., 3 boxes (Box 42-44)
    - Voting rights, 1970-1976. (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Absentee voting, 1974-1975. (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Voting Rights Act, 1981-1982, 1985, 1990. (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - District of Columbia voting rights, 1981, 1984-1985. (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Voting Rights Act monitoring project, 1981. (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Voting Rights Act monitoring project, 1982. (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Voting Rights Act monitoring project training conference, 3-4 February 1982 (folder 1 of 2). (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Voting Rights Act monitoring project training conference, 3-4 February 1982 (folder 2 of 2). (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Voting Rights Act monitoring project, 1984-1986. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - LWV-RKO Voter Drive, October 1983, February-August 1984. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - LWV-RKO Voter Drive, no month 1984. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Commission to Increase Voter Registration. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Advocate for the Voter, 1988-1989. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Voter registration, 1988-1990. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Voter registration, 1992-1993. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Voter registration, 2004. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Motor Voter, 1989, 1991. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Motor Voter, 1994-1995. (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Motor Voter lawsuits. (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Take Back the System, January-May 1991. (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Take Back the System, June-December, no month 1991. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Take Back the System, 1992. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Take Back the System printed materials, 1992. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Early/absentee voting, 1994. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Lawsuit, 1995. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Electronic voting, 2003-2006, 200[-]. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 4: Redistricting/Reapportionment., 2 boxes (Box 44-45)
    - Reapportionment/redistricting, 1950-1952. (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Reapportionment/redistricting, 1958-1961. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Reapportionment/redistricting, 1962-1963. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Committee for Fair Representation, 1962-1965. (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Reapportionment/redistricting, 1964. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Reapportionment/redistricting, 1965-1966. (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Reapportionment/redistricting, 1981. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Reapportionment/redistricting, 1982-1985, 1988. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Reapportionment/redistricting, 1990-1991. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Reapportionment/redistricting, 2008-2009. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 5: Legislature., 2 boxes (Box 45-46)
    - Legislature, 1955. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Legislature, 1962-1963, 1965. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Legislature, 1967. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Legislature, 1968. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Legislature, 1969, 196[-]. (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Legislature, 1970-1974. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Legislature, 1975-1979. (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Legislature, 1980-1981. (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Legislature, 1982-1983. (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Legislature, 1984-1985. (Box 45, Folder 14)